automedia.com 2013-12-19

# Privacy Policy - autoMedia

autoMedia.com is a wholly owned business unit of autoMedia Solutions Inc., a privately held company. Thank you for visiting our website, www.automedia.com, and trusting us to assist you with your new car research and purchase, and your automobile driving and ownership experience. autoMedia.com is committed to protecting your personal and private information that you provide to us when visiting our website. Our privacy policy pertains to the information that we collect and receive from you such as when you send us an email, request a quote, and/or enter a contest or sweepstakes.

**Terms and Conditions of Use**

autoMedia.com assists consumers who are interested in researching and purchasing a vehicle, in obtaining opinions, research, pricing and availability information on their vehicle of choice, from one of our partner lead distributors. By submitting your information to this service for the purpose of receiving a price quote, or by entering a contest or sweepstakes offer on our website, you agree to the following:  

  * You are an adult 18 year of age or older. Children under the age of 13 are ineligible to enter any personal information about themselves or others, request a new vehicle price quote, or participate in forums, contests or sweepstakes.
  * You currently reside in the United States of America.
  * You grant permission to autoMedia.com and their lead partners to forward your information to a participating automotive retailer
  * You grant permission to the designated automotive retailer to contact you via email and/or telephone to follow up on your purchase/price-quote request, or contest/sweepstakes entry should you win.
  * You are submitting your information for the purpose of engaging an automotive retailer in a discussion about purchasing a vehicle.
  * You are not soliciting services or products for sale.
  * You have voluntarily submitted your information and have not received any monetary compensation for doing so.

## How We Safeguard and Use Your Personal Information

autoMedia.com and their lead partners do not share or sell your personally identifiable information to any third party except for the designated participating automotive retail dealer(s).

By submitting your personal information, you expressly grant permission to autoMedia.com and their lead partners, to forward it to participating retail automotive dealer(s) for the purpose of engaging in dialogue via email and/or telephone regarding the purchase of a vehicle.  

We may provide your personal information if required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to conform to the law, and to protect and defend our rights and property. 

When entering a contest or sweepstakes, you agree to provide autoMedia.com and any third-party merchant relative to any contest or sweepstakes with accurate, complete registration information. Your registration must include your real name and accurate information. Each registration is for your personal use only and not on behalf of any other person or entity. We do not permit any other person using any personal information form or section under your name, nor do we permit access through a single name being made available to multiple users on a network. You are responsible for preventing such unauthorized use. 

Additionally, by submitting your information to autoMedia.com, you agree that: the service is provided "as is." The individual dealer(s), and not autoMedia.com and their lead partners, who received your information, are responsible for any information, price quotes, or promises they provide to you, and for their actions products and services, autoMedia.com does not make any guarantees, warranties, or representations of any kind with respect to dealer services, and they expressly disclaim any and all implied warranties including, without limitation, those of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose. 

autoMedia.com, like most websites, uses an Internet technology known as “cookies” to obtain information from our visitors and their use of our site. This information includes the date and time of visitor use of our site, the particular pages viewed and the time spent viewing those pages. This information, similar to “web analytics” and “behavioral targeting” helps us to evaluate and improve our site according to patterns of visitor use. Our third party advertisers may also use these methods and other web coding called “web beacons” to help them determine which advertisements users have responded to. 

autoMedia.com includes a forums and areas for users to provide comments on our website. Any information you disclose in those sections may become available to the general public. Do not include any personal information that you would not want other parties to view or access. If you include any personal information, such as your email address, address or telephone numbers and receive unsolicited contact from third parties, autoMedia.com cannot be held responsible. 

Authorized autoMedia.com employees and their lead partners may access your information only for the following purposes:

  * To respond to a specific customer service issue initiated by you.
  * To respond to a specific customer service issue initiated by the designated participating automotive retail dealer who received your information.

Authorized autoMedia.com employees may aggregate information for internal marketing and business operations purposes. In these instances, your personally identifiable information is not revealed, nor is it shared with any third parties.

### WHAT DO WE DO WITH COLLECTED INFORMATION?

We use the personal information you provide to allow you to make product purchases, to fulfill your requests, improve our website, products and services, to send you promotional offers related to autoMedia.com or our business partners, and to operate our business. A user may, at any time, opt out of receiving promotional offers by mail or e-mail. How You Can Control Your Personal Information. We also use collected information to evaluate and administer our products and services, respond to any problems that may arise, difficulties in navigating our sites or accessing certain features, as well as to gauge user trends to determine what products and services are most popular with users, and to put you in touch with fulfillment partners who can provide services that we cannot. We allow users of our website to send articles or links by e-mail to other parties who may be interested in them. We do not retain any e-mail addresses of either the sender or recipient of such articles or links after they are sent, and do not share "send a friend" e-mail addresses with third parties.

Authorized automotive dealers have agreed to not share or re-sell your personal information to any third party. However, the dealer and its agents or vendors may use the information submitted by you to solicit your business related to the normal business of a factory authorized automotive retailer. Furthermore, authorized dealers have also agreed to abide by all federal, state, and local, laws and regulations applicable to automotive retailing and privacy issues. autoMedia.com and their lead partners expressly disclaim any and all implied warranties and cannot guarantee compliance by the dealer.

autoMedia.com and their lead partners do not collect information for the purpose of obtaining credit information, nor does it forward your information to Credit Bureaus.

#### Third-Party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/index.aspx)

If you have any questions or concerns regarding the autoMedia.com policies set forth above, please contact us at: 

**Phone: 310.212.0395  
Email Us**

**Trademark and Copyright Information**

Every asset (text and images) on autoMedia.com is copyrighted (unless otherwise noted) and may not be used except with our written permission. Use of any information on our website by you or other third parties without prior permission is prohibited and may violate copyright, trademark, and privacy laws.
